ELIJAH DANKO

Senior Software Engineer



+48-538-941-416 elijahdanko.net



elijahdanko



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Overall, nine years of working experience in the field. Have participated in various technologies and programming languages, including C, C++, Java, Clojure, Javascript, and Python. Started as a system engineer and was moving to the Web, and Golang, in particular. I'm strongly focused on business' needs, and as a Free Software user, considering contributing further back to Open Source.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Aigent

Dec 2019 - Ongoing

Amsterdam, NL

- Troubleshooting high performing components.
- Design, develop and maintain services and internal tools.
- · Refine existing parts.
- · Collaboration with clients.

Senior Software Engineer

Omnisend

Feb 2018 - Dec 2019

Lviv, UA

- Design, develop and maintain high performing services.
- Write unit, acceptance and e2e tests.

Senior Test Engineer

Here

Jun 2017 - Feb 2018

Lviv, UA

- Design and develop integration testing framework.
- Implement and maintain integration tests.

Middle Software Engineer

Cisco

■ Nov 2015 - Jun 2017

Lviv, UA

- Develop and maintain gateway systems for embedded devices.
- Develop and maintain primitive components and drivers, such as, VOIP, IPTV, VPN.
- Write user guides and other technical documentations.
- Maintain and extend the testing framework solution with tests.

Junior Software Engineer

Inside Secure

Jul 2013 - Nov 2015

Lviv, UA

- Develop and maintain a stereotyped simulator for credit card vendors.
- Write and maintain integration tests.

TECH STACK

General Purpose Languages

Golang design, prototype and implement real time, low latency microservies, using rest api, rpcs, protobuf messages, write command line tools. Embed C libraries (cgo).

write and maintain applications including character and network devices for embedded equipment, create ffi libraries for other languages.

Javascript design, prototype and implement microservices exposing rest api, protobuf, etc. Implement Ecma5,6 compatible applications, support react applications.

Clojure | implement command line tools, rest api services.

Python | scripting, maintain testing framework using sqlite3, road algorithms (djaextra).

C++ | implement and support gui tools (qt4), maintain nfs testing framework.

Java maintain visa, mastercard nfs testing framework.

Domain Specific Languages



LANGUAGES

English			
Ukrainian			

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Economics

Volodymyr Dahl East Ukrainian National University

Sep 2010 - Jun 2013